insideview.com 2014-09-26

# Privacy - InsideView

This policy is effective as of March 18, 2014.

Your privacy is very important to InsideViewTM. This Privacy Policy was prepared because we believe you should know as much as possible about InsideView’s practices. It describes the information we collect on, or make available through, [www.insideview.com](http://www.insideview.com/) (the “Site”), what may happen to that information, the security measures that we use, your rights with respect to your information stored or displayed in or through the InsideView Service and collected in connection with your use of the Service or the development of our Database and Service.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you are welcome to contact us as provided in the Contacting Us section of this Privacy Policy or by visiting our Website at [www.insideview.com/contact-us](http://www.insideview.com/contact-us/).

InsideView has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this Privacy Policy and InsideView’s practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers the site [www.insideview.com](http://www.insideview.com/). TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@insideview.com](mailto:privacy@insideview.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request) and if necessary initiate TRUSTe’s dispute resolution process.

Any capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy are defined in the Terms of Use [www.insideview.com/terms](http://www.insideview.com/terms/).  
  
**1) Information We Collect for Our Database**

**Information We Collect**

InsideView develops and maintains a database (the “Database”) of company and individual profiles (“Profiles”).

Information collected for the development of an individual Profile and/or published in an individual Profile on the InsideView Service may include: name, title, company, current position, prior position, salary, publications, articles by, about, or quoting an individual, links to social media postings by or about the individual, professional contact information and similar information.

Information collected for the development of a company Profile and/or published in a company Profile on InsideView may include: the name and title of the company’s officers and certain company employees, information obtained from the company or published by third parties.

**Our Sources of Information**

InsideView collects information about individuals and companies from a variety of publicly available and other sources, such as company websites, company blogs, non-confidential corporate records or reports (for example, SEC filings), press releases, news articles, magazines, social media sites, and other content published by or on behalf a company or published by data brokers or third parties in accordance with their terms and conditions for the collection, disclosure and sharing of information.

InsideView also collects information about individuals and companies from government publications in accordance with their terms and conditions for the disclosure and sharing of information.

InsideView may also receive some Information directly from the individual or company whose Profile is featured in our Database.

Finally, subscribers and other third parties who know facts about a particular individual or company may contribute some information to our Database about that individual (name, title, email, phone, social profile link (Facebook and Twitter)) or company (name, URL, address, phone, industry, revenue, employee count) if they desire.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

This information collected as described above is then compiled, edited and organized through InsideView’s unique proprietary CRM Intelligence application in order to create a Profile for each individual or company

Each individual or company Profile is integrated into the InsideView Database, which is part of the InsideView Service. Subscribers of the InsideView Service have access to the Database and the Profiles and, as such, may conduct searches and save the identified Profiles meeting their search criteria for their own internal purposes. Subscribers may also contact individuals or companies using the contact information contained in Profiles. For example, an InsideView subscriber may use the InsideView Database in order to identify the specific individual who may be a decision maker in a company, and then contact the individual in order to offer goods or services for sale to the company.

Limited access to the InsideView Database is provided at no cost, whereas full access to the Database is subject to the payment of a subscription fee.

**2) Information We Collect From Our Subscribers and Visitors**

**Information Our Subscribers Provide About Themselves or Their Business**

Our primary goal in collecting personal information from subscribers of the InsideView Service is to provide them with a smooth and efficient experience while communicating with us and using InsideView. This allows us to provide customized services and features that are most likely to meet subscribers’ needs and that make their experience easier and quicker.

When an individual expresses an interest in obtaining information about InsideView or registering to use the Service, InsideView requires the individual to provide us with contact information such as name, company name, address, phone number, and email address. InsideView may then use the contact information provided to reach the individual via email or phone.

When a subscriber purchases services, InsideView may require the subscriber to provide financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, payment/credit card number, and the number of employees within the organization that will be using the Service. InsideView may also ask for additional information, such as company annual revenues, number of employees, or industry.

**Payment Card Information**

InsideView does not retain payment or credit card numbers. This information is passed on immediately to our payment card processing service, which is required to use this information only for the processing of each specific transaction.

Once registered for the Service, a subscriber is able to add companies to his or her watch lists and automated search agents. We will retrieve and share information of interest to a subscriber, such as noteworthy events, address, phone number, and names of contacts on the companies that the subscriber wishes to watch.

**Information Our Subscribers may Provide for the Lead Referral Program**

If a subscriber chooses to use our lead referral service to refer a third party to our site, the subscriber must first ensure that his/her business partner has agreed to share their contact or other information with us. In this case, we will ask for the third party’s contact name, email address and phone number. We will use this information to contact the third party (example, via a one-time email or phone call) about becoming a subscriber of InsideView. InsideView stores this information for the sole purpose of following up on the lead and tracking the success of our referral program.

The third party may contact us to request that we remove his/her/its information from our lead referral contact list. See the Contacting Us section of this Policy for contact details or visit our website at [www.insideview.com/contact-us](http://www.insideview.com/contact-us/).

**Usage Data We Gather**

We also receive and store certain types of information whenever an individual (subscriber or visitor) interacts with our Site. InsideView automatically receives and records information on its server logs from the individual’s browser including the individual’s IP address, browser type, date/time stamp, InsideView cookie information, the page(s) that the individual requested, and the referring/exit pages.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small amounts of data sent to an individual’s browser from the InsideView Web servers and stored on the individual’s hard drive. InsideView uses cookies to deliver content specific to the individual’s interests and to keep track of user names and passwords during user sessions. If an individual chooses not to accept cookies, his or her ability to use InsideView might be limited. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information.

Generally, our Service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show

Our Site also contains third party cookies and other tracking technologies. The use of cookies or other tracking technologies by our tracking utility companies is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our third party tracking utility companies use session ID cookies to make it easier to track how many times individuals have visited a certain page on the site.

Our third party tracking utility companies employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), which they use in combination with their cookies. These beacons help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. The use of clear gifs by our tracking utility company is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our subscribers’ personal information.

**Correspondence**

If an individual corresponds with InsideView via email, or other method regarding his or her activities or postings on the Site, InsideView will treat that email or other correspondence as ordinary business correspondence and will retain it according to its standard corporate information retention policies.

**3) Our Use and Disclosure of Subscriber Information**

Except as set forth in this Policy or under express permission from the subscriber, at no time will we share the personal information that subscribers submit for InsideView access with anyone, including other subscribers.

**Subscriber’s Permission**

When subscribers provide us with personal information to include in a published individual Profile about the subscriber or any information to include in a published company Profile, the subscriber gives us permission to use and disclose that information for the purpose of providing the InsideView Service as described above.

**Subscribers’ Information**

We use information we maintain about subscribers and other information we obtain from our subscriber’s current and past activities on the Site: (1) to perform the InsideView services requested, including emailing administrative and service notifications; (2) for marketing purposes (such as contacting subscribers to discuss interest in InsideView, and sending promotional communications or other information regarding InsideView and its partners, that may be customized based on usage patterns; (3) to check financial qualifications or collect payment; (4) to operate and improve the Site, including using aggregated Site usage data to understand utilization and improve the Service; (5) to resolve disputes; (6) to troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of Use; and (7) to allow subscribers to post comments within the blog section of the Site as well as submit testimonials and allow us to post these statements and testimonials along with the subscriber’s name on the Site.

Subscribers should be aware that any information provided in these areas may be read, collected and used by others who access them.

Subscribers may contact us to request removal of personal information from our blog or testimonials. See the Contacting Us section of this policy for contact details. As a subscriber, in some cases we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**IP Addresses**

InsideView uses IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site. Generally, IP addresses tell us the location from which a person is connecting to us, what service provider the person is using, and which parts of the Site the User is visiting. We reserve the right to track IP addresses for the purposes of fraud prevention, and we reserve the right to release IP addresses to legal authorities.

**Behavioral Targeting / Re-targeting**

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites.  Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here](http://preferences.truste.com/).  Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising.  You will continue to receive generic ads.

_NOTE:   Participant may also link to the NAI opt-out mechanism _[ ** _http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp_**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**To whom we may Disclose Information**

InsideView may need or be required by law or legal process to disclose information about visitors, subscribers or Profiles to third parties. This includes: (a) to actual or potential parties to a lawsuit that InsideView is or may become involved in as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights; (b) to comply with a facially valid judicial or governmental subpoena, warrant, or other order or legal process served on InsideView by a court or a government institution that has asserted its lawful authority to obtain the information; (c) if InsideView reasonably believes that such disclosures will potentially mitigate its liability; or (d) to enforce or defend its rights or any of its policies (such as the Terms of Use Agreement).

**Disclosure to Service Providers**

InsideView may engage third parties to perform necessary business functions on its behalf, such as outside contractors or service providers (e.g. hosting company, consultants) for example, in connection with communications to users, payment processing and other aspects of Site operations. If it is necessary to perform their functions, these third parties may have access to Individual or Company information or Profiles. These third parties are required not to use any information or Profile for any purpose other than to provide services to InsideView. They are also required to protect the information and Profiles with adequate reasonable security measures.

**Transfer to Acquirer or Successor entity**

Finally, if InsideView sells a substantial portion of its assets or is acquired, reorganized, merged into another entity, goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, it is likely that subscriber, Profile and other business information (including the InsideView Database) will be one of the business assets transferred in connection with such a transaction. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that any acquirer or successor of InsideView or its assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this Policy. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

**Outbound Links**

InsideView contains links for subscribers to access other sites. InsideView is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage subscribers to review the policies of these sites.

**Social Media Features**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and hosted apps that launch the social media sites. These Features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our site and may set a cookie in order to enable the Feature to function properly. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**4) Opting Out, Accessing, Correcting, Updating, and Removing Information**

**Additions, Corrections – Individuals**

Any individual has the right to obtain access to the Profile and Information that we hold about him or her.

If the individual determines that the Profile is incomplete or that factual information about him or her or the company is incorrect (e.g., wrong college degree), he or she may propose an addition or correction. We will accept and implement the proposed addition or correction upon receiving adequate proof of the authenticity and accuracy of the supplied information and if the supplied information meets our selection criteria and internal policies regarding information collected for the creation of Profiles.

To request access, addition or correction of your Profile information, please contact us as indicated in the Contacting Us section below, or visit our website at [www.insideview.com/contact-us](http://www.insideview.com/contact-us/). We will respond promptly in accordance with our internal policies on access, addition or correction to Profiles and sources of information.

**Additions, Corrections – Subscribers**

Subscribers may update or change their registration information (and their Profile) by editing their user or organization record. To update a user Profile, please click on “My Profile” or email us at [support@insideview.com](mailto:support@insideview.com) if you require any assistance.

**Opting Out – Individuals**

An individual has the right to request that InsideView unpublish, remove, or make unavailable to third parties any information about him or her from the InsideView Databases or disconnect a link to another site. We will respond promptly in accordance with our internal policies on access to Profiles.

To request that InsideView unpublish your Profile or remove a link, please contact us as indicated in the Contacting Us section below or visit our website at [www.insideview.com/contact-us](http://www.insideview.com/contact-us/).

Please note that while access by general subscriber population will be discontinued, we may retain and use some or all Profile information as necessary for the management of our Database (for example, to identify your name and profile as blocked from publication) or to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

**Opting Out – Subscribers**

Subscribers may opt-out of receiving promotional communications by contacting us at [support@insideview.com](mailto:support@insideview.com). Subscribers of our Free services agree to receive our promotional communications while continuing to use such Services at no cost. Free Service subscribers electing to unsubscribe from receiving our promotional communications, will no longer be able to access our Free Service.

Individual subscribers designated as “administrators” may not opt out of receiving administrative notices, which are not promotional in nature.

If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you with services contact us at [support@insideview.com](mailto:support@insideview.com).

**Companies**

The authorized representative of a corporation or other business or entity (other than a natural person) may obtain access to the Company’s Profile and be informed about the source of the information used to create that Profile.

If an authorized corporate representative determines that the Profile of the entity is incomplete or factual information about the company is incorrect, he/she may propose an addition or correction or deletion. We will accept and implement the proposed addition or correction or deletion upon receiving adequate proof of the authority of the individual to request a correction or deletion on behalf of the entity and proof of the authenticity and accuracy of the supplied information and given the supplied information meets our selection criteria and internal policies regarding information collected for the creation of Profiles.

**5) Security**

InsideView uses industry standard security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction of the information under our control. We have taken measures to protect personal information once it is received by or available through the Site, including but not limited to the following: limited and controlled access by employees, servers and data stored in a secured location, security software and hardware (such as firewalls, encryption, Secure Socket Layers) where appropriate and cost effective.

User passwords are used to secure access to the InsideView Service and subscriber information. We encrypt the transmission of user IDs and passwords using Secure Socket Layers (SSL).

As a subscriber, you may choose to have InsideView remember you on your computer; InsideView will automatically log you in by storing your user ID (but not your password) in a cookie in your browser. Our login page provides a service for subscribers to obtain a new password in case they forget their password.

When subscribers enter sensitive information (such as payment/credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

While we do our best to implement reasonable security measures, we do not guarantee that our safeguards will always work. InsideView will not be liable for unauthorized disclosure of Profile or other information that occurs through no fault of InsideView, including, but not limited to, error in transmission, misuse of a subscriber’s password and login credentials, a subscriber’s failure to comply with its security obligations, and the unauthorized acts of InsideView’s employees. Transmissions protected by industry standard technology and administered by humans cannot be guaranteed to be secure.

**6) Single Sign On**

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.

**7) Safe Harbor Statement**

InsideView has certified that it abides by the Safe Harbor privacy principles as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, storage, use, transfer and other processing of personal information transferred from the European Economic Area (“EEA”) or Switzerland to the U.S. InsideView’s Safe Harbor certification can be found on the U.S. Department of Commence Safe Harbor List. For more information about the Safe Harbor principles, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>. InsideView will take steps to remedy any problem arising out of a failure to comply with the Safe Harbor principles. InsideView may not be required, however, to take any action contrary to applicable law.

**8) International Transfers**

Personal information held in the InsideView Database may be transferred, stored, maintained, and processed in the United States or in other countries where we have facilities or where we have engaged a service provider. This storage, maintenance or processing will be performed under privacy and security laws and standards that may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you have any concern about the above, you can have your Profile removed or unpublished from our Databases as explained above.

**9) Notification of Changes to the Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy so individuals are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If however, we are going to use individual personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by posting a notice on our Site, or comply with other procedures as required by applicable laws, prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy policy practices.

**10) Contacting Us**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact InsideView by sending email to [privacy@insideview.com](mailto:privacy@insideview.com), or by mail to: InsideView

Attn: Privacy Officer

444 De Haro Street, Suite 210

San Francisco, CA 94107

If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request) and if necessary initiate TRUSTe’s dispute resolution process.

**11) Special Terms Applying to Profiles**

INSIDEVIEW IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE TO ANY INDIVIDUAL OR COMPANY FOR THE ACCURACY, CONTENT, COMPLETENESS, LEGALITY, RELIABILITY, OR AVAILABILITY OF THE PROFILE INFORMATION OF THAT INDIVIDUAL OR COMPANY.

PROFILE INFORMATION IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER, EXPRESS, IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW.

IN NO EVENT SHALL INSIDEVIEW OR ITS LICENSORS HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO ANY INDIVIDUAL OR COMPANY FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY FORM HOWEVER CAUSED UNDER ANY OTHER THEORY OF LIABILITY, WITH RESPECT TO THE CONTENT, USE, AVAILABILITY, OR UNAVAILABILITY, OF THE PROFILE INFORMATION OF THAT INDIVIDUAL, OR FOR ANY OTHER REASON. THE FOREGOING DISCLAIMER SHALL NOT APPLY TO THE EXTENT PROHIBITED BY APPLICABLE LAW.

InsideView operates in the State of California. Its practices with respect to the handling of Profile or Personal Information are governed by the laws of the State of California, except for its conflicts of law principles, and will be subject to the sole and exclusive jurisdiction and venue of the courts seated in San Francisco, California, USA.
